birthdaysnewyork.com 2010-12-09

# Privacy Policy

**WEBSITE PRIVACY DISCLOSURE**

**Company Policy:**   
The privacy of your nonpublic personal information is important to us. We use safeguards to protect your privacy and confidentiality. This Disclosure discusses information we collect and the manner in which it is used. 

Birthdaysnewyork.com reserves the right, at any time, to add to, change, update or modify our privacy policy simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website. 

**Security**  
Birthdaysnewyork.com maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

**Information Collection**  
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Website and read the information contained on the Web pages, we may gather certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We may automatically gather the Internet domain (for example, "companyx.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "myschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain), IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our Website, and the date and time you access our Website and the pages you visit. 

Birthdaysnewyork.com may collect nonpublic personal information from you when you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information to us though our Website, such as when ordering services/products and accessing account specific or other profile information. We may collect information about your transactions that we secure from our files and from our affiliates. We may collect information that we receive from consumer reporting agencies. We may collect information that we receive from others involved in your transactions, such as real estate agents or lenders. We limit use of such information to the purposes for which the information was provided. However, we reserve the right to use such information for marketing/product development research and other similar purposes and/or to contact you regarding additional services or products that you may find useful. 

If you send an electronic mail (e-mail) message that includes personally identifiable information, for example, in an e-mail message containing an inquiry, we will use that information to respond to your inquiry. Remember that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication is very sensitive, or includes information such as your bank account, charge card, or social security number, you should not send it electronically unless it is encrypted or our Website indicates the particular site is secure. 

Birthdaysnewyork.com may use "cookies" to improve our service to you. Cookies may help us recall a previous visit. The cookies we use do not collect personally identifiable information, and we do not use them to determine your identity. If you are not comfortable with this use, you may configure your browser to be notified when cookies are to be received and to provide you with the option of refusing cookies. However, refusing cookies may limit your ability to use our Website in its entirety. 

**Employees**  
Our employees may view information that you provide us in order to perform their jobs and service you. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. Sharing We do not share nonpublic personal information to third parties who are not affiliated with us, unless the law allows us to do so. WE DO NOT DISCLOSE ANY NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU WITH ANYONE FOR ANY PURPOSE THAT IS NOT SPECIFICALLY PERMITTED BY LAW. 

**Marketing**  
We may disclose any information that we collect about you to our affiliates or nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law. We also may disclose information about our customers or former customers and others to the following types of nonaffiliated companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or with whom we have joint marketing agreements: Financial service providers such as companies engaged in banking, consumer finance, securities and insurance. Non-financial companies such as envelope stuffers and other fulfillment service providers. Links to other Websites Our Website may contain links to Websites that are provided and maintained exclusively by third parties Websites provided and maintained by third parties are not subject to this privacy policy. Please review the privacy policies on those Websites to understand their personal information handling practices. We make no representations concerning the privacy policies of these third party Websites. 

**Questions**  
If you have questions about our privacy policy, you may contact our webmaster at [administrator@Birthdaysnewyork.com](mailto:administrator@citybartenders.com "mailto:administrator@citybartenders.com"). Please provide the webmaster with information about the specific Website that you are inquiring about.
